ezarticleinformation.com 2009-12-24

# Privacy Policy | EZ Article Information

EZArticleInformation.com strives to protect user information while still sharing the wealth of knowledge and content available. Our use of your personal information is detailed in this privacy policy. 

We will never sell, trade, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party. 

In addition to forms you fill out on the site, EZArticleInformation.com collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. This is basic and common practice, such as verifiying an IP address, or using cookie technology which will remember you during your visit, to keep you from re-entering your password or seeing an advert repeatedly. You can elect to set your browser not to accept cookies, though this may interfere with your use of the site. 

Visit data and collective information (information that does not personally identify you) is collected and analyzed to be used in various ways. None of this will include your personal identifying information. This refers to tracking user behavior to determine, for example, popular pages or statistical information useful for advertisers. 

We of course will use your personal information to communicate solely with you about your account, our policies, and services and products offered by [www.ezarticleinformation.com](http://www.ezarticleinformation.com/ "www.ezarticleinformation.com"). This also includes site administration, ecommerce transactions, troubleshooting, account  
maintenance. 

In our business development, we may sell, partner, merge, or buy another business, in which case your personal information may be included as an asset. We may disclose your information when we believe we are required to do so by law, and may not provide notice in such case. 

This privacy policy is only for our site, and does not concern the policies of our affiliates, partners, advertisers whom you may link to from our site. EZArticleInformation.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. 

EZArticleInformation.com may only be used by individuals age 13 or older, and will not collect information knowingly of any children ages 12 or under except as permitted by law. If we are aware we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, this information will be deleted. 

EZArticleInformation.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Use of this site constitutes agreement to this policy as stated during time of use. 

##### Permalink
